# ONOSE OGBIDI

### FRONT-END DEVELOPER



- +234 907-173-8136
- ogbidionose@gmail.com
- Rivers State, Nigeria
- https://onoseogbidiportfolio.netlify.

## PROFILE

As a Front-End Developer with 3 years of experience, I specialize in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, with 1 year in React. My creative and analytical skills enable me to build engaging, user-friendly web experiences. A proactive team player with excellent communication skills, I am dedicated to driving innovative solutions in collaborative projects.

# STACKS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Typescript
- Node JS
- Express
- Mongo DB

# EXPERIENCE

#### WEB CONTENT MANAGER(VOLUNTEER)

The Carpenter's Church

June 2022 - October 2022

- Developing and maintaining web applications using Wordpress and other related technologies.
- Updated the website regularly in audio messages, photos, videos and checking the buying and selling of audio messages on the website.

## IT SPECIALIST INTERN

Aveon Offshore Limited

February 2024 - April 2024

- Developing and maintaining web applications using Wordpress and other related technologies.
- Expanding my React.JS knowledge
- Provide technical support to end-users, including troubleshooting hardware, software, and network issues.
- Evaluate, install, and maintain software applications and updates.

# EDUCATION

#### **SECONDARY SCHOOL**

Jephthah Comprehensive sec school 2013 - 2019

#### COMPUTER ENGINEERING

University of Benin

2019 - Present